Tufts Criterion UP053
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Tufts Criterion, 1968 -- 1993; UP053.001; 2.4 Linear Feet; 8 Volumes
  - Criterion, Fall, 1992; UP053.001.010.00001 (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. Jumbogravure - Alumni day photos; [Alumni association] Linda Dixon takes on twofold mission for Tufts' trustees, Cynthia McCarthy set to build bridges from alumni, Jumbogravure [inlcudes photos]; [Adventures in Veterinary Medicine] Veterinary Medicine: not a job yet, but an adventure. pp. 10, 11. [Alumni 1992] Alumni team up on a new weekly, p. 12. Jumbogravure - Alumni Day photos, p. 20-23. Class of 1932 attends 60th reunion with vigor - attendees listed, p. 24. The Perennials of '27 celebrate 65 years - attendees listed, p. 24. Class of '37: Quite a group at 55th reunion - attendees listed, p. 25. [Alumni 1992] Class of '67 does 25th reunion their way - attendees listed, p. 30. Friendships renewed by Class of '72 at 20th - attendees noted, p. 31. Class of '77's 15th draws far-ranging crowd, p. 32. Class of 82 sees big changes at 10th reunion, p. 33. Fifth reunion celebrated in style by Class of 87, p. 34. [Alumni 1992] A year of preparation pays off for class of 42- 100+ class members listed, p. 26. Class of 1947's 45th reunion is memorable - attendees listed, p. 27. A great weekend; Class of 62's 30th reunion - attendees listed, p. 29. Enthusiastic group comes to Class of 52's 40th - attendees listed, p. 28. 35 years flew by for Class of 57 reunioners - attendees listed, p. 29.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1993; UP053.001.010.00002 (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni association] Distinguished service awards; [alumni association] Alumni gathering in the field; Winter 1993
  - Criterion, Spring/Summer, 1993; UP053.001.010.00003 (Box 10)
    Additional user copy in the Reading Room. [Alumni/ae] "Tuftonia's Feast" [photos included], Jumbofest [photos included], Black alums meet on campus [photo]; [Alumni/ae] Medical school celebration; [Alumni relations] A tufts time-frame, Tufts mastercard, "Tuftonia's fest", "Jumbofest", "Tuftonia's day"; [Alumni long distance advantage] Tufts mastercard; [Alumni council] Enlightenment series "Romeo and Juliet"; [Alumni association]Senior awards presented and Distinguished service awards presented, Inaguration of John Dibiaggio, A Tufts time, Tufts Mastercard; [African-American Center] Black alums meet on campus, p. 16. Shirley Aidekman (photo). Meet the Trustees. [Alcivar-Warren, Acacia] Betting on Nature.
  - Criterion, Fall, 1993; UP053.001.010.00004 (Box 10)
    [Alumni weekend] Jumbogravure [photos]; [Alumni relations] Debra Metcalfe seeks to build alumni connections; [Alumni council] Cultural events planned for fall; Alumni council plans fall meeting; [Alumni association] Seeking those who have served, Jumbogravure [includes photos], Symposium taps 100 years of women; [Adel Abu-moustafa] Linkage emerges between Saudi Arabia and Medical, Dental School. [Administration 1993] Miaoulis named associate dean.
  - Criterion, Winter, 1993; UP053.001.010.00005 (Box 10)